The most explosive shooting experience on iPhone!

Described by the press as "incredible"; "an achievement", "it looks and sounds absolutely fantastic".

Play as a soldier of the 101st Airborne in the most intense WWII battles:
 - The iPhone version of the world-famous Brothers In Arms franchise.
 - 14 missions in 3 campaigns: Normandy, Ardennes & Tunisia.
 - Unbelievable 3D graphics recreating the atmosphere of a real Hollywood WWII blockbuster.
 - Drive a 4x4 vehicle or a Sherman tank and use a wide range of weapons (bazooka, sniper rifle, machine guns, etc.)
 - Use the accelerometer function to launch grenades & the touch screen to shoot at enemies.

Soldier, defeat is not an option.
