"The benchmark of the action-adventure games on next-gen consoles lands for the first time on your iPhone and iPod touch.

-------------------
""This game looks better on the iDevices that it did on the Nintendo DS. The models are crisper. The textures are brighter and cleaner. The animation seems smoother, too, such as when Altair transitions from creeping along in stealth mode to slashing apart a guard with his sword. The cutscenes are fluid and detailed. Gameloft also added a lot of voice to the game, too, adding an extra element of character to Altair."" -- IGN
-------------------

Jerusalem, 1191 AD. The Third Crusade between the Crusaders and Saracens is tearing the Holy Land apart.
You are Altaïr, a Master Assassin sent by the Order of the Assassins on a quest to find “The Chalice”, an object of such power that it can end the Crusades, depending on which camp owns it. Steal The Chalice from the Templars before someone offers them the right price for it.
The fate of the Holy Land depends on you...

Plunge into this direct prequel to the critically acclaimed game title, Assassin's Creed™, offering rich gameplay and a well-balanced mix of stealth, chaotic action, and riddle-solving exploration in the midst of fully 3D-rendered historical environments of the Crusade's Middle East.

- Master the assassin's skills to benefit from a wide range of acrobatic moves and perform impressive combo attacks, mixing sword skills and kicks.

- Choose your fighting tactics based on 6 weapons for both close combat and long-range attacks: Swords, daggers, grappling hook, and bombs.

- Skill-based mini-games put your patience & dexterity to the test: Perform pickpocket maneuvers to carefully steal precious items from the crowd and make informants speak.

- Unique dramatic tension on iPhone, intensified by 3D cinematic cutscenes and characters' voices.

- Collect orbs to upgrade health and weapons.

Recommended for fans of action, adventure, and historical games."


