Take revenge on bankers in this fast-paced castle defense game. Defend the White House and save the US taxpayers’ money before it gets stolen! It’s time for you to give them what they deserve!

- The most topical and humorous castle defense concept ever!
- It’s your only chance to really take revenge on bankers for the recession they caused
- Earn money to buy spectacular defenses and upgrades including a sniper, a tank or Uncle Sam!
- Explore many different ways to beat bankers: tap, grab or shake them in the air
- 5 different enemies to fight with ground and air units including helicopters and vacuum bankers
- Accessible to everyone, whether you are right- or left-handed 


For fans of Stickwars, Fieldrunners and Defend your Castle
Other Gameloft games you may like: Siberian Strike, Let’s Golf!, Real Soccer 2009, Real Tennis 2009, Asphalt 4 and Ferrari GT: Evolution

Published and developed by Gameloft.
