Think you know everything about brain training? Think Again! 

"If only real-life education could be as fun as this ace brain trainer." - PockerGamer.co.uk (8/10 & Silver Award)

Brain Challenge 2: Think Again! is the latest entry in the most comprehensive brain training franchise on iPhone and iPod touch, providing a total brain workout. Train your brain in the classic brain exercise categories: Memory, Visual, Logic and Math as well as innovative categories exclusive to Gameloft’s Brain Challenge franchise: Stress Training, Focus and never seen before on iPhone, Visual training.

• A total of 43 mini-games ensuring hours of fun brain challenge
• 30 mini-games to boost your math, logic, memory and focus skills
• 5 mini-games to reduce stress and help you relax
• Never before seen on iPhone: Visual Training mini-games to prevent eyesight loss
• 3 bonus mini-games
• 4 coaches and an improved chart system ensuring the most personalized brain development program
• A remodeled interface that displays player avatars and brain usage percentages
• Cute and fresh graphics make this game candy for the eyes

Follow us on twitter for exclusive info on Brain Challenge™ and other Gameloft games:
http://twitter.com/BrainChallenge_