On the heels of the award-winning Real Football and Let’s Golf, Gameloft now releases the best 3D tennis game on iPhone/iPod touch! 
Live the life of a professional player on a world tour where the only goal is to become number one!

• 8 players entirely modeled in highly detailed 3D graphics.
• From Paris to New York to Stockholm, play in 7 stadiums on 3 different surfaces – clay, grass and synthetic – each providing a different experience. 
• Local Wi-Fi Multiplayer to challenge your friends in real time! 
• Controls making the most of the iPhone/iPod touch capabilities.
• Serve by tilting your iPhone!
• A wide array of strokes for a deeper experience: Lob, drop shot, smash and more.
• A Career mode that lets you join a tennis tour just like a real professional player.

Recommended for fans of arcade and simulation sports games.

Published and distributed by Gameloft.