Get ready to call "UNO" on your iPhone!

Play the classic card game that's #1 for fun with friends and family. In single or multiplayer, playing UNO™ has never been so fun and easy, thanks to a brand new gameplay system! Simply drag & drop cards using your finger on the screen for intuitive control, and be the first to get rid of all your cards.
 
- All your favorite Action Cards are here: Wild, Reverse, Draw 2 and more! 
- Customize your game with 9 different rules including 7-0 and Jump-in. 
- Enjoy a unique multiplayer mode! Play UNO™ all over the world online or with your friends through a Wi-Fi connection.   
- Take on increasingly hard challenges in Tournament Mode.
