The only game on iPhone/iPod touch that allows you to play guitar & drums like a Rock God!
""It’s certainly worth the price, and one of the best music games to make it to the iPhone."" - MacWorld, 4/5
""A lot of fun to play."" - AppVee, 5/5

In Guitar Rock Tour FREE, play with the hit ""Rock You Like A Hurricane"" on the hottest Miami concert stage. Tap your screen to the beat of the track: don't miss a note or you'll hear it and be booed off the stage!

FULL VERSION FEATURES:
- 2 instruments to play: guitar & drums.
- 17 world famous licensed rock songs, including:
> Beat It
> Message in a Bottle
> Rock You like a Hurricane
> Smoke on the Water
> In the Shadows
> Girlfriend 
> Heart-Shaped Box
> Banquet
> You Really Got Me, and more!
- Console-like 3D graphics and high-definition sound quality.

Ready to fire up the crowd with Guitar Rock Tour?

Other recommended music game: DJ Mix Tour

Published and distributed by Gameloft.

** Follow Guitar Rock Tour on Twitter and be the first to know about exclusive news and updates, competitions, gifts, and more! http://twitter.com/GuitarRockTour
** Friend us at www.facebook.com/gameloft
