Follow the official Twitter account to get more info about the game: http://twitter.com/BrainChallenge_

The #1 Brain Training Simulation

""Brain Challenge for the iPhone/iTouch is superb. If you have an iPhone, you need this title!"" -GenerationGamerz

MSN, MTV, Yahoo, Google are all talking about it, too! Download the full version now.

FULL VERSION KEY FEATURES

43 mini-games, 8.7/10 average in reviews, 5 awards.
Brain Challenge is the ONLY comprehensive brain training partner on the iPhone or iPod Touch:

-Train in the following categories: Visual, Memory, Logic, Math, and Focus.

-Develop personal tools to help prevent stress.

-Explore your creativity.

-Rotate the iPhone to move cubes using gravity in an exclusive mini-game.

-Simply touch the correct answer.

-Monitor your progress with detailed status charts.

Transform your iPhone into a personal coach, and turn tedious waiting time into a fun yet educational gaming session anywhere!

""I would highly recommend this game for all ages."" -iphonebuzz
Also recommended to fans of quiz, trivia, IQ, or puzzle games and anyone concerned with brain stamina and mental health.

Follow us on twitter for exclusive info on Brain Challenge and free games.
http://twitter.com/brainchallenge_
