Try out the LITE version of Siberian Strike. Choose one of three pilots and enjoy this fast-paced shoot’em up.  

FULL VERSION KEY FEATURES
 - Fast-paced action, intense combat and 4 difficulty levels to keep you constantly challenged.
 - Unique gameplay mixing shooting and insane piloting missions that test your dexterity.
 - Choice between Accelerometer and Touch controls that let you steer and target enemies like a real pilot.
 - Choose from 3 ace pilots and customize their planes with 12 different colors.
 - Join your friends in frenetic local Wi-Fi Multiplayer to experience a crazy adventure.
 - Gigantic boss fights and memorable moments with immersive 3D animations.
 - 12 amazing levels to explore across varied environments: canyons, secret bases, tunnels, and more!

DOWNLOAD THE FULL VERSION NOW!

Follow the official Twitter account to get more info about the game: http://twitter.com/Siberian_Strike 

Published and distributed by Gameloft

