Join the Resistance on Twitter: www.twitter.com/TS_wirelessgame
The best soldiers will be granted exclusive news, updates, competitions, gifts, and more!

----------------------------------------
IGN: ""It was impossible to walk away unimpressed with the production values""
----------------------------------------

Assume the role of John Connor, leader of the Resistance, in post-apocalyptic 2018 Los Angeles. Battle for survival against the forces of Skynet in a breathtaking 3D third-person shooting game inspired by the already cult, sci-fi movie.
Counter hordes of enemies in concentrated armed combat, destroy specific targets, hack computers, drive futuristic vehicles, defend areas and more.
The high variety of missions and gameplay, plus the faithful rendering of the movie universe, will definitely delight gamers and fans of the Terminator universe alike!

Plunge into the heart of the battle with the FULL version:
- Play as John Connor and Marcus Wright, each having their own strengths and special abilities.
- 4 different controls that take advantage of the iPhone-specific touch screen and accelerometer to fit any playing style.
- Counter hordes of 11 different enemies sent by Skynet, including some exclusive models exclusively designed for the iPhone & iPod touch game.
- 6 weapons from shotgun to surge cannon and grenade launcher
- 360° view of 3D environments through 8 levels.
- Play as a T-600 in an unlockable game mode.

You're the only hope to stop Skynet.

For fans of Terminator and survivors of the Judgement Day, but also recommended for fans of action, adventure, shooting and hack 'n slash games.
Other Gameloft games you may like: Brothers In Arms, Hero of Sparta, Assassin's Creed.
