Get ready to relive the thrill of Super Bowl XLIII as the Cardinals or Steelers in NFL 2010 Free.

- Intuitive controls: Move your player with the virtual pad, perform moves by touching the appropriate icon, and punch a hole through the other team’s play!
- A large selection of playbooks with over 200 plays to choose from
- 3D graphics worthy of the best handheld console simulations with players and stadiums entirely modeled in 3D
- Audio commentary during the match

With the FULL version, enjoy a 100% authentic NFL experience with all the real teams, all the real players, and all the real action. So, whether you’re a fan of the Giants, Cowboys or Packers, you will be able to lead your favorite team through an entire season.

Don’t play football – live it.

-------------------------------------------------------

Are you an NFL fan, or want to know everything about this game? Follow us on Twitter: www.twitter.com/NFL_2010
For fans of the NFL, football, sports games or big tackles and unreal passes.
Other Gameloft games you may like: Let’s Golf!, Real Soccer 2009, Real Tennis 2009, Asphalt 4 and Ferrari GT: Evolution.
Published and developed by Gameloft.
