After centuries of peace, Hell’s gate has been rebuilt and the Empire of Darkness has been reborn. A new war is inevitable…

Try out the FREE version of Rise of Lost Empires, the new Real-Time strategy game for the iPhone, and discover its beautiful heroic-fantasy environments. 

FULL VERSION KEY FEATURES
- A true real-time strategy game: Colossal armies to lead, cities to build, and resources to manage
- 2 campaigns – one with humans, the other with Orcs – that will keep you playing for many hours
- Controls perfectly customized for playing on the iPhone
- More than 20 units to control and 20 different buildings to construct
- 6 heroes with tremendous strength and magical powers to lead your armies
- A variety of beautiful heroic-fantasy environments

DOWNLOAD THE FULL VERSION NOW!

Follow the official Twitter account to get more info about the game at: http://twitter.com/RiseLostEmpires 

Published and distributed by Gameloft
