See how fun (and addictive) Diamond Twister is in this Lite version composed of 3 enchanting levels!  

Described as “one of the more addictive examples of the match-three genre when it comes to iPhone puzzling” with a score of 8/10 by Pocketgamer, the leading authority in mobile gaming.

A hugely addictive, simple, and intuitive puzzle:
Swap pairs of gems to line up 3 or more identical diamonds.

EXCLUSIVE FEATURES FOR THIS MOST PRECIOUS GAME: 
• Rotate your iPhone… Gems fall from everywhere!
• Dazzling visual effects, gem explosions, and twisting diamonds.
• 8 game modes and 64 different levels of difficulty in 8 glamorous environments.

Twist Diamonds.
Twist your iPhone.
Twist your mind!

