"Card games are such a natural fit for iPhone. Uno is no exception, with intuitive touchscreen controls and pleasant presentation. Multiplayer, however, serves up a wild card that transforms this classic card game from blue to red hot."" - Bronze Award / PocketGamer.com

Get ready to call ""UNO"" on your iPhone!

Play the classic card game that's #1 for fun with friends and family. In single mode, playing UNO™ has never been so fun and easy, thanks to a brand new gameplay system! Simply drag & drop cards using your finger on the screen for intuitive control, and be the first to get rid of all your cards.
 
FULL VERSION FEATURES:
Play UNO™ anytime on your iPhone! Get access to Gameloft Live to enjoy UNO™ online with your friends.
- All your favorite Action Cards are here: Wild, Reverse, Draw 2 and more! 
- Customize your game with 9 different rules including 7-0 and Jump-in. 
- Enjoy unique multiplayer mode! Play online or with your friends through a Wi-Fi connection.  
- Take on increasingly hard challenges in Tournament Mode.

Recommended for fans of board and card games.

Follow the official Twitter account to get more info about the game: http://twitter.com/UNO_Gameloft

Published and distributed by Gameloft.
