War is hell. Step inside.

 “The word 'stunning' comes to mind when playing Modern Combat: Sandstorm. Gameloft's jaw-dropping shooter will have you blinking in disbelief.” Pocketgamer

 

Modern Combat: Sandstorm, Gameloft’s new action-thriller will plunge you into the heart of modern war. Assigned to Mission Sandstorm, your duty is to locate and annihilate a new terrorist cell setting up shop and recruiting foreign insurgents in a remote desert hot spot. This jarring first person shooter will equip you with the most sophisticated and powerful modern day weapons.
 
FULL VERSION KEY FEATURES

§ 10 missions featuring varied and highly polished Middle Eastern environments (city, hospital, sewers, port, lab, training camp etc...)

§ Intuitive iPhone controls offer unprecedented game fluidity. Choose among 3 different control systems: Default Controls, Screen Tap and Virtual Sticks 

§ Use a wide range of authentic, advanced weapons (2 assault rifles, sniper rifle, RPG, shotgun, submachine gun, light machine gun, heavy machine gun mounted on a moving 4X4, explosive grenades, flashbang grenades, radiation detector) enriched with a leveling system that allows the player to progressively unlock weapons and use munitions from fallen foes 

§ Aim and shoot with extra precision in Sniper and Ironsight mode 

§ Highly polished 3D graphics provide full immersion into the military experience and high intensity combat

§ Cinematic snippets, military voice-overs and true-to-life situations increase game realism

 
Brace yourself for war like you’ve never experienced it before.

Follow the official Twitter account to get more info about the game: http://twitter.com/Modern_combat/
