Try out the free version of Real Football 2010, - the #1 football game on the App Store and discover the thrill of the greatest football matches: Barcelona vs. Manchester or Brazil vs. Spain! 

Features of the full version:

EVEN MORE CONTENT
- 8 leagues, 245 teams and real players’ names thanks to the FIFPro license
- Voice commentary for a TV-like broadcast of the match
- 14 stadiums entirely modeled in 3D to the slightest detail
 
NEW ONLINE REAL-TIME MULTIPLAYER
- Go head-to-head with friends online (Wi-Fi) or in local mode (Bluetooth + Wi-Fi)
- Take part in official matches with Gameloft LIVE! to improve your ranking
 
NEW GAME MODES
- Enter The Legend: Play as your favourite player on the field during the whole match and manage your career as a pro football star
- Club Master: Take part in a whole season with your favourite team and strengthen it through trades
- RF League: Online leaderboard to compare your performance with other Real Football players over the world
 
YOUTUBE VIDEO UPLOAD
Upload your best replays directly to YouTube, rate the videos of the community on www.real-football.com and try to be selected for the Top 10 of the month.
 
FOOTBALL RSS FEED
Football RSS feed to get all the latest football scores directly from the game’s main menu.
 
ONLINE UPDATE OF THE DATABASE
Download the most recent player database to always keep your game up to date with the latest transfer news.
 
IMPROVED CONTROLS
- New direction pad for a more precise football experience.
- Select your player easily by touching him on the screen.
 
Get ready for a total football experience!

------------------------------------------

Are you a football fan, or want to know everything about this game? Follow us on Twitter: www.twitter.com/real__football.
Become a fan of Gameloft on Facebook: www.facebook.com/gameloft

------------------------------------------

For fans of football, sports games, Steven Gerrard, bicycle shots in the top corner of the net or highly-powerful 30m shots.
Other Gameloft games you may like: Let’s Golf!, NFL 2010, Real Tennis 2009, Asphalt 4 and Ferrari GT: Evolution.

------------------------------------------

Optimised graphics on the 3GS and on the 3rd generation iPod touch.


Published and developed by Gameloft.
