Join the elite circle of Ferrari car owners and take part in exclusive races around the globe in the truest and most immersive racing game on iPhone. 

• 33 authentic Ferrari car models: the new Ferrari California, F430, Enzo Ferrari, F40, Testarossa, 250 GTO, and more. 
• A multiplayer mode to challenge your friends in heated car races. 
• 3 control modes (including motion detection) for varied and realistic driving sensations. 
• Complete courses on a circuit to obtain your driver’s license. 
• Great sense of freedom as you travel across 7 famous cities (Madrid, Athens, etc.) choosing your own path at every crossroad. 

Make your dream come true... drive your own Ferrari car.


In the next update: An online multiplayer mode to face drivers from all over the world.

To ensure optimal functioning of this driving game, please make sure to reset your iPhone or iPod touch (hold down the Sleep/Wake button and the Home button at the same time for 10-15 seconds) after installing this game. Once your iPhone or your iPod touch has restarted, you can run the game normally.

