Want to play poker in good company? Choose the first and unique sexy poker game on iPhone!

Challenge and undress 6 incredibly alluring women, "all drawn exceptionally well by talented artists" (IGN.com), inspired by the hottest sex symbols.

THE SEXIEST FEATURES:
- Shake your iPhone or touch the screen to make their lovely breast bounce!
- 3 game modes for hours of sensual entertainment: 5-card draw poker, video poker, and blackjack.
- Deal with the girls' realistic, challenging different playing styles.
- A photo gallery, to quickly access all the pictures.

Think you hold all the cards in this game? They have something different in mind!
