Experience all the craziness of New York Nights: success in the city on Twitter
http://twitter.com/new_york_nights

The best selling social simulation game on mobile is finally available for your iPhone and iPod Touch. Praised by the press, New York Nights is far from your traditional social sim.

“There is always something to do, it's easy to play... (to) advance the story, and the game has a wonderful sense of humor.” IGN
“Attractive, funny and definitely worth a fling - just don't tell the wife.” Pocketgamer (8/10 silver award)

You arrive in Manhattan fresh off the plane with little more than the shirt on your back and a place to crash. Make friends, find profitable employment, and party hard to kick-start your new life in this interactive social sim. 

- Explore 6 renowned New York neighborhoods (5th Avenue, Greenwich, Wall Street, Times Square, Chinatown and Central Park) with beautifully rendered backgrounds and visuals.
- Get immersed in the New York atmosphere thanks to characteristic New York personalities like the Naked Cowboy, and activities like a picnic in Central Park or finding a roommate.
- Engage NPC’s through an intuitive interactive system allowing you to talk, flirt, offer gifts, offend, steal and much more.
- Experience a story full of humor and crazy twists and turns.
- Make your own life choices which will affect the outcome of the game, ensuring the utmost freedom in your social adventure.