The #1 Brain Training Simulation

 
"Brain Challenge for the iPhone/iTouch is superb.  If you have an iPhone, you need this title!" -GenerationGamerz
 
MSN, MTV, Yahoo, Google also are all talking about it!

43 mini-games, 8.7/10 average in reviews, 5 awards.

Brain Challenge is the ONLY comprehensive brain training partner on the iPhone or iPod Touch:

-Train in the following categories: Visual, Memory, Logic, Math, and Focus.

 
-Develop personal tools to help prevent stress.
 
-Explore your creativity.
 
-Rotate the iPhone to move cubes using gravity in an exclusive mini-game.

-Simply touch the correct answer.
 
-Monitor your progress with detailed status charts.

Transform your iPhone into a personal coach, and turn tedious waiting time into a fun yet educational gaming session anywhere!

""I would highly recommend this game for all ages."" -iphonebuzz

Also recommended to fans of quiz, trivia, IQ, or puzzle games and anyone concerned with brain stamina and mental health.

